Made you look, take 2, lights,camera, action
--
♪ I could have my Gucci on ♪
-- 我可以穿上華麗的 Gucci
♪ I could wear my Louis Vuitton♪
-- 我可以穿上高級的 LV
♪ But even with nothin’ on ♪
-- 但即便我什麼都沒穿上
♪ Bet, I made you look (I madeyou look) ♪
-- 我敢說你的目光還是離不開我
♪ I’ll make you double take ♪
-- 當我從你面前走過
♪ Soon as I walk away ♪
-- 你一定會被我的魅力震懾住
♪ Call up your chiropractor ♪
-- 打給你的脊椎治療師
♪ Just in case your neck break ♪
-- 以免你為了看我脖子扭到
♪ Ooh tell me whatcha, whatcha,what you gon’ do (ooh)? ♪
-- 快告訴我，告訴我，告訴我你想做什麼
♪ ‘Cause I’m ‘bout to make ascene ♪
-- 因為我準備要引起大家的注意了
♪ Double up that sunscreen ♪
-- 多塗一層防曬霜
♪ I’m ‘bout to turn the heat up♪
-- 我準備讓這裡的溫度升高
♪ Gonna make your glasses steam♪
-- 讓你的眼鏡朦上霧氣
♪ Ooh tell me whatcha, whatcha,what you gon’ do (ooh)? ♪
-- 快告訴我，告訴我，告訴我你想做什麼
♪ When I do my walk, walk ♪
-- 當我以曼妙姿態向你走
♪ I can guarantee your jaw willdrop, drop ♪
-- 我能保證你的下巴會掉到地上
♪ ‘Cause they don’t make a lotof what I got, got ♪
-- 因為他們總低估我所擁有的魅力
♪ Ladies if you feel me, thisyour bop, bop! (bop bop, bop!) ♪
-- 女孩們，如果你懂我在說什麼，這首歌就是獻給你的
♪ I could have my Gucci on(Gucci on) ♪
-- 我可以穿上華麗的 Gucci
♪ I could wear my Louis Vuitton♪
-- 我可以穿上高級的 LV
♪ But even with nothin’ on ♪
-- 但即便我什麼都沒穿上
♪ Bet, I made you look (I madeyou look) ♪
-- 我敢說你的目光還是離不開我
♪ Yeah, I look good in myVersace dress (take it off!) ♪
-- 當我穿上我的高級裙子，我看起來美極了
♪ But I’m hotter when my morninghair’s a mess ♪
-- 但當我早上起床頂著一頭亂髮時，我看起來更火辣
♪ But even with my hoodie on ♪
-- 因為即便我只是穿著普通的連帽衣
♪ Bet, I made you look (I madeyou look!) ♪
-- 我敢說你的目光還是離不開我
♪ And once you get a taste ♪
-- 當你品嚐我的魅力後
♪ You’ll never be the same ♪
-- 將會改變你的人生
♪ This ain’t that ordinary ♪
-- 這並不常見
♪ It’s that 14 karat cake ♪
-- 有如高級的甜點
♪ Ooh tell me whatcha, whatcha,what you gon’ do (ooh)? ♪
-- 快告訴我，告訴我，告訴我你想做什麼
♪ When I do my walk, walk ♪
-- 當我以曼妙姿態向你走
♪ I can guarantee your jaw willdrop, drop ♪
-- 我能保證你的下巴會掉到地上
♪ ‘Cause they don’t make a lotof what I got, got ♪
-- 因為他們總低估我所擁有的魅力
♪ Ladies if you feel me, thisyour bop, bop! (bop bop, bop!) ♪
-- 女孩們，如果你懂我在說什麼，這首歌就是獻給你的
♪ Oh I could have my Gucci on(Gucci on) ♪
-- 我可以穿上華麗的 Gucci
♪ I could wear my Louis Vuitton♪
-- 我可以穿上高級的 LV
♪ But even with nothin’ on ♪
-- 但即便我什麼都沒穿上
♪ Bet, I made you look (said, Imade you look) ♪
-- 我敢說你的目光還是離不開我
♪ Yeah, I look good in myVersace dress (take it off!) ♪
-- 當我穿上我的高級裙子，我看起來美極了
♪ But I’m hotter when my morninghair’s a mess ♪
-- 但當我早上起床頂著一頭亂髮時，我看起來更火辣
♪ But even with my hoodie on ♪
-- 因為即便我只是穿著普通的連帽衣
♪ Bet, I made you look (said, Imade you look!) ♪
-- 我敢說你的目光還是離不開我
Meghan Trainor! Aha, you're apopstar.
-- Meghan Trainor! 妳是一個超級偶像
You're an icon, you're themoment
-- 妳是一個象徵，妳是目光焦點
What other words are you?
-- 還有什麼可以形容妳
Uhh. That's it, anyway, we'regoing to post in 13 minutesexactly, don't miss it
-- 嗯，無論如何，我們13分鐘後要發表了
Hashtag Made You Look, hashtagAlly, don't ask about that one
-- 我會把妳tag上去，嗯，別問了
Are any of your dancers single?Don't answer that. Ok
-- 有任何妳的舞者單身嗎？別回答
Be professionalSorry
-- 專業些，抱歉，
We're going to do it one moretime for my account, andyou're going to do it better
-- 我們再做一次，把它做更好
Alright, one more time?
-- 好，再一次？
Just do it. Just do it.
-- 做就對了
I made you look
--